(Leonard:)...as a purely intellectual exercise.
What do you mean?
Well, ah, remember when you tried to learn
how to swim using the Internet?
(Sheldon:)I did learn how to swim.
(Leonard:)On the floor.
The skills are transferable.
(Sheldon:)I just have no interest
in going in the water.
(Leonard:)Then why learn how to swim?
(Sheldon:)The ice caps are melting, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)In the future,
swimming isn't going to be optional.
(Sheldon:)But you do bring up an interesting point.
I don't have to break new ground here.
I'm sure the research already exists.
No. No, my point is
if you wanna learn how to make friends...
(Leonard:)...then just go out to a coffee shop
or a museum.
(Leonard:)Meet people. Talk to them.
Take an interest in their lives.
(Sheldon:)That's insane on the face of it.
(Penny:)- Come on.
- Where are we going?
(Sheldon:)You're driving me to the mall
to acquire a book...
(Sheldon:)...that summarizes the current theories
in the field of friend making.
(Leonard:)Why don't you just lie down on the floor
and swim there?